

CONTACT



Address

16 Duiker Road,...Cape Town, 7769



Email

kanyisomadlebe@yahoo.com



Phone 064-747-3024

CERTIFICATES

- Data Science Foundation
- Big Data Foundation
- Beyond the Basics: Istio and IBM CKS

EXPERIENCE

UVUAFRIKA Learnership | 2023 - 2023

UVUAFRIKA Internship | 2023 - Current

KANYISO MADLEBE

Information Technology

ABOUT ME

An ICT graduate specializing in Business Analysis, equipped with practical experience from a software development learnership, and currently engaged as a Junior Software Developer. I'm dedicated to ongoing learning, adaptable to challenges, and poised to bring innovation to development projects while striving for excellence in the field.

EDUCATION

Information Technology

Walter Sisulu University | 2020 - 2022

 Diploma in ICT in Business Analysis.

Matric

Khanyisa High School | 2019

• Grade 12.

REFERENCE

Mr R.Ngandu HOD at WSU-IT|047 4016232

Thandi Ndaba Candidate Manager| 084 806 3374

Mrs NP.Madlebe Mother | 0733 348 4983